/**
 * Copyright (c) 2004-2008 Blue Whale Systems Ltd. All Rights Reserved. 
 * DO NOT ALTER OR REMOVE COPYRIGHT NOTICES OR THIS FILE HEADER 
 *  
 * This program is free software; you can redistribute it and/or 
 * modify it under the terms of the GNU General Public License version 
 * 2 only, as published by the Free Software Foundation.  
 *  
 * This software is provided "as is," and the copyright holder makes no representations or warranties, express or
 * implied, including but not limited to warranties of merchantability or fitness for any particular purpose or that the
 * use of this software or documentation will not infringe any third party patents, copyrights, trademarks or other
 * rights.
 * 
 * The copyright holder will not be liable for any direct, indirect special or consequential damages arising out of any
 * use of this software or documentation.
 * 
 * See the GNU  General Public License version 2 for more details 
 * (a copy is included at /legal/license.txt).  
 *  
 * You should have received a copy of the GNU General Public License 
 * version 2 along with this work; if not, write to the Free Software 
 * Foundation, Inc., 51 Franklin St, Fifth Floor, Boston, MA 
 * 02110-1301 USA  
 *  
 * Please contact Blue Whale Systems Ltd, Suite 123, The LightBox
 * 111 Power Road, Chiswick, London, W4 5PY, United Kingdom or visit 
 * www.bluewhalesystems.com if you need additional 
 * information or have any questions.  
 */



NAME BWPL

#include <eikon.rh>
#include <eikon.rsg>
#include <avkon.rh>
#include <avkon.rsg>

#include "BlueWhalePlatform.hrh"


// ---------------------------------------------------------
//   
//    Define the resource file signature 
//    This resource should be empty.
//
// ---------------------------------------------------------
//
RESOURCE RSS_SIGNATURE { }

// ---------------------------------------------------------
//   
//    Default Document Name
//
// ---------------------------------------------------------
//
RESOURCE TBUF r_default_document_name { buf = ""; }

// ---------------------------------------------------------
//   
//    Define default menu and CBA key.
//
// ---------------------------------------------------------
//
RESOURCE EIK_APP_INFO
    {
	// Each of our views has its own menubar and cba
	// so don't define any here or you'll get a weird
	// painting issue where screen below shows through
	// because app is allocating twice the space for CBA's.
    menubar = r_BlueWhale_menubar;
    cba = R_AVKON_SOFTKEYS_OPTIONS_EXIT;
    }

RESOURCE MENU_BAR r_BlueWhale_menubar
{
titles =
    {
		MENU_TITLE {menu_pane = r_BlueWhale_menu;}
    };
}

RESOURCE MENU_PANE r_BlueWhale_menu
{
items =
    {
    MENU_ITEM {command = 123; txt = "App menu";}
    };
}

// ---------------------------------------------------------
//   
//    Extra string buffer resources.
//    Note: These must come at the end in order to 
//	  not cause a panic on app startup, because the base AppUI
//	  expects the generated rsc file to look a certain way at the top.
//
// ---------------------------------------------------------
//

